Guide to the Irish Echo Photographs AIA.045
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Film, Television, and Theatre, 1952, 1970-2004; 6.19 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, 1 card box, and 1 oversized flat box
  - Subseries VI.A: Film and Television, 1952, 1970-2001
    - Age of Innocence, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - American Masters, undated (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - An American Werewolf in Paris, undated (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - Arcadia, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Bad Behavior, undated (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Ballykissangel, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Barb Wire, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Bedtime Story, 1990, undated (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Before and After, undated (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Being John Malkovich, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - Benny and Joon, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - Black Cat White Cat, 1987, circa 1999 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - Black Robe, 1991, undated (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Blink, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Blown Away, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Bossanova Blues, undated (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - The Boxer, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Braveheart, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - The Break, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - The Brothers McMullen, 1995, undated (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Buffalo Baker, undated (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Carrington, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Caught, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 8, Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Cement Garden, undated (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Chaplin, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Circle of Friends, undated (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Clay Pigeons, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - The Closer You Get, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - The Commitments, 1991, undated (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Cool World, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - The Crying Game, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Dancing at Lughansa, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - A Dangerous Woman, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Daredevils and Dreamers, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - A Day in the Life of Ireland, 1991, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - The Dead, circa 1987-1988, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Dead Man, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Dead Man Walking, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Deceived, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - December Bride, 1994, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - The Devil's Own, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Divine Comedy, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Divine Rapture, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Dusk Till Dawn, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - East is East, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Eat the Peach, 1987, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - The End of the Affair, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - The Englishman Who Went Up a Hill But Came Down a Mountain, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Ethan Frome, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - An Everlasting Piece, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Far and Away, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 20, Box 20, Folder 10)
    - The Field, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 11, Box 11, Folder 21)
    - The Fighting Fitzgeralds, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Film Fleadh, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Film and Television: General, undated (Box 20, Folder 12, Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Film and Television: "A", 1998, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Film and Television: "B", 1993-1994, 2002, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Film and Television: "C", 1992 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Film and Television: "D", 1992, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Film and Television: "F", 1999 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Film and Television: "G", 1993 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Film and Television: General, 1997-1998, undated (Box 11, Folder 29, Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Film and Television: "I", 1987, 1989, 1991-1992, 1994, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Film and Television: "J", undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Film and Television: "L" (includes radio), 1989, 1992, 1994, 1998, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Film and Television: "M" (includes radio), 1990, 1993-1999, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Film and Television: "N", circa 1970s, 1993, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Film and Television: "O" (includes radio), 1995, 2001, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Film and Television: "P", 1992, 1994, 1999-2000, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Film and Television: "Q" and "R", 1952, 1992-1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Film and Television: "S", 1989, 1992, 1994, 1998, undated (Box 11, Folder 38, Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Film and Television: "T", 1994, 1997-2000, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Film and Television: "U" and "V", 1992, 1995-1996, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Film and Television: "W", 1989, 1994, 1998-2001, undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Film and Television: "X," "Y" and "Z", 1998 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Flubber, undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Forces of Nature, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Four Weddings and a Funeral, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Frankenstein, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Frankie Starlight, 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - From Dusk Till Dawn, 1996, undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - The General, 1998, undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - The Gingerbread Man, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 50, Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Go Now, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Golden Eye, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - A Good Man in Africa, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - The Good Thief, undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Goodwill Hunting, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - The Great White Hype, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Green Fingers, undated (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Grosse Point Blank, undated (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Guiltrip, undated (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Gulliver's Travels, 1996, undated (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Hear My Song, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Henry V, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Hidden Agenda, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Home Alone, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - The Horse Whisperer, undated (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Hush-A-Bye Baby, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - In Dreams, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - The Informer, undated (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - In The Mood For Love, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - In The Name of the Father, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Interview With The Vampire, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Into The West, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Irish In America, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Ironweed, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - It's A Wonderful Life, undated (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - I Went Down, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 14, Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Jack and Sarah, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - J.F.K., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Joe Gould's Secret, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Kicking and Screaming, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Korea, 1996, undated (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Kundun, undated (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - The Land Girls, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - A League of Their Own, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Leprechaun, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Les Miserables, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 86, Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 87, Box 20, Folder 16)
    - London Kills Me, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - A Man of No Importance, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - The Matchmaker, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 90, Box 20, Folder 17)
    - The Mexican, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Michael Collins, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 91, Box 20, Folder 19)
    - A Midnight Clear, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - The Miracle, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Mr. Bean, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - My Left Foot, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - The Odd Couple II, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - The Real Blonde, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Patrick Brave Sheperd of the Emerald Isle, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - A Play in the Fields of the Lord, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - Saving Private Ryan, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 22, Box 11, Folder 97)
    - The Searchers, undated (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - The Secret of Roan Inish, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - She's So Lovely, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - She's The One, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Schindler's List, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - A Simple Twist of Fate, undated (Box 11, Folder 102)
    - Sleeping With The Enemy, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - Sliding Doors, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - The Snapper, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 104)
    - Some Mother's Son, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Someone to Watch Over Me, 1987 (Oversize 22, Folder 20)
    - Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace, undated (Box 20, Folder 26, Box 11, Folder 106)
    - State of Grace, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - This Is My Father, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Waking Ned Divine, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Wilde, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Subseries VI.B: Theatre, 1970-2004
    This subseries consists of photographic prints of popular Irish and Irish American theatre productions staged in Ireland, primarily Dublin, and in the United States, primarily New York. Featured in this subseries are photographs of significant works including Martin McDonagh's The Beauty Queen of Leenane, Samuel Beckett's Waiting for Godot, and Brian Friel's Dancing at Lughnasa. Photographs of several Shakespearean productions, including Hamlet, King Lear, and A Midsummer's Night Dream, are also included. The majority of photographs featured in this subseries were taken between 1980 and the early 2000s.
    - Ah, Wilderness!, undated (Box 11, Folder 108)
    - An American Storyteller, undated (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - Arcadia, 1986, 1997, undated (Box 11, Folder 110)
    - Arms and the Man, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 111)
    - Arrah-na-pogue, undated (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - Away Alone, undated (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - Bar and Ger, undated (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - Barry Lyndon, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - The Beauty Queen of Leenane, circa 1985-1988, 1998, undated (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - Being Irish, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Blood, undated (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Blood Brothers, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Bobby Sands, 1992, undated (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - A Bogus Christmas Story, undated (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Bronx Irish at the Ramparts, undated (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Candida, undated (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - The Clearing, undated (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - Cloudstreet, undated (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Coming Through, undated (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - Coming Times, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Contact with the Enemy, undated (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - A Couple of Blagaurds, 1993, undated (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Da, 1988, undated (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Dancing at Lughnasa, undated (Box 11, Folder 130, Box 18, Folder 2, Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Dancing At Lughnasa: Various Productions, circa 1990s (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Dancing on Dangerous Ground, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Death of a Salesman, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Des, undated (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - Desperations, undated (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Dirty Day, undated (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - The Donahue Sisters, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 135, Folder 165)
    - The Donkey Bar, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - Down the Flats, undated (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Down the Garden Path, undated (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Dubliners, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Electra, undated (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - End Game, undated (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - The Factory Girls, undated (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Fairytale of New York, undated (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - Finnegan's Farewell, undated (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Finnegan's Wake, 2004; TW_AIA_045_ER_2
    - Flaherty's Widow, undated (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - From Sea to Shining Sea, undated (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - God Willing, undated (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Going East on Ashland, undated (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - Gold in the Streets, 1986, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - Golden Boy, undated (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - Grandchild of Kings, undated (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Gross Indecency, undated (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Great Catherine, Theatre Row Theatre, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Hamlet, undated (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Happy Days, 1996, 1998-1999, undated (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Heartline, undated (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - Henry VI, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 156)
    - Holiday, undated (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Honesty is the Best Policy, undated (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - The Hostage, undated (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, undated (Box 11, Folder 160)
    - The Investigation, undated (Box 11, Folder 161)
    - Irish Arts Forum, undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - The Judas Kiss, undated (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - Juno and the Paycock, undated (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - King Lear, undated (Box 11, Folder 164)
    - Krapp's Last Tape, 1986, 1996, undated (Box 11, Folder 165)
    - A Leap of Faith, undated (Box 11, Folder 166)
    - Long Day's Journey into Night, undated (Box 11, Folder 167)
    - Lord of the Dance, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - The Matchmaker, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - McDonagh, Martin and Julie Ormand, undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, undated (Box 11, Folder 168)
    - A Moon For The Misbegotten, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - My Astonishing Self, undated (Box 11, Folder 169)
    - New Irish Theatre Group, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - A Night in November, undated (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Riverdance: Various Productions, 1995-2001 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Riverdance Red Carpet, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Stones in His Pocket, undated (Box 20, Folder 34, Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Sycamore, undated (Box 11, Folder 171)
    - Theatre, undated (Box 20, Folder 35, Box 29, Folder 16, Box 34)
    - Theatre: "A", 2001-2004, undated (Box 11, Folder 172)
    - Theatre: "B", circa 1970s, 1987, 2002, undated (Box 11, Folder 173, Box 18, Folder 15-17)
    - Theatre: "C", 1980, 1988, 2000-2002, undated (Box 18, Folder 18-22, Box 11, Folder 174)
    - Theatre: "D", 1987, 1989, 1995-1996, 2002, undated (Box 11, Folder 175)
    - Theatre: "E", 1988, 1995-1999, undatd (Box 11, Folder 176)
    - Theatre: "F", 1997, 2003, undated (Box 12, Folder 1, Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Theatre: "G", 1993, 2000, 2002, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Theatre: General, circa 1970s-2001, undated (Box 18, Folder 10, Box 12, Folder 3, Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Theatre: "H", 1996, 2001, 2003, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Theatre: "I", 1985, 1988, 1991, 1993, 2002, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Theatre: "J", 1988, 1992, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Theatre: "K", 1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Theatre: "L", 1992, 2000-2001, undated (Box 18, Folder 11, Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Theatre: "M", 1996-1997, 2000, 2002, undated (Box 18, Folder 37-41, Box 12, Folder 9, Folder 12-13)
    - Theatre: "N", 1988, 2002, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Theatre: "O", undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Theatre: "P", 1982, 1986-1988, 1993-1996, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Theatre: "R", 1994, 2001-2004, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Theatre: "S", 1982, 1993-1997, 2000-2003, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Theatre: "T", 1982, 1987, 1995-1998, 2000-2003, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Theatre: "U" and "V", 1986, 1999, 2002, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Theatre: "W", 1994-1999, 2003, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Theatre: "X," "Y" and "Z", undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - This Is My Father, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - A Thousand Acres, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Translations, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Twelve Dreams, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Veronica Guerin, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Waiting for Godot, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Series VII. Individuals, circa 1960-2004; 6.70 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 3 card boxes, 3 manuscript boxes, 1 oversized flat box, and 1 half manuscript box
  This series consists of photographic prints of various Irish, American, and Irish American individuals. Included in this series is extensive photographic documentation of Roman Catholic clergy from all levels of rank. Additionally, this series features individuals who resist strictly defined categorization (either by qualifying for multiple categories or for none at all) and who can be regarded more generally as public figures of varying degrees of importance. One example is the late Connie Doolan, a celebrated Irish immigration activist; former New York imports representative for Guinness; and a highly successful businessman. Rather than constrain him to a single identifying characteristic, as is the structure for Series I-VI, Doolan is featured in Series VII. Another example is that of Veronica Guerin, who was both a journalist and an activist, and thus is also featured in Series VII.
  This series is unique to the rest of the collection in terms of its ordering scheme. Series VII follows a strict alphabetical arrangement with a general alphabetic sequence dispersed throughout, rather than clustered. For example, following the general "A" folder are the folders for promiment individuals with surnames beginning in A; following that is the general "B" folder and then folders for prominent individuals with surnames beginning in B, continuing through "Z".
  - "A", circa 1970s, 1981, 1987, 2001, undated (Box 18, Folder 14, Box 12, Folder 25, Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Allen, Myrtle, 1993-1994, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - "B", circa 1970s, 1987-1996, 2002, undated (Box 12, Folder 27, Box 18, Folder 15-17, Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Beirne, Frank, 1977, 1988, 1991, undated (Box 12, Folder 28, Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Benson, Sean, 1989, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Brennan, Robert, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Brosnan, Pierce, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Burke, Bill, 1990, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Burke, William J., 1977, 1988-1989, 1993, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Byrne, Gay, undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - "C", circa 1970s, 1985, 1988-1989, 1995-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 31, Box 18, Folder 18-22, Box 26)
  - Campbell, Father Colm, 1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Carter, Angela, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Clergy: General, circa 1970s, 1982-1985, 1987-1995, 2001, 2003, undated (Box 12, Folder 34, Box 18, Folder 23-24)
  - Clergy: Brothers, circa 1970-1977, 1981-1988, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Clergy: Hierarchy, circa 1970s, 1982-1990, 1996, 2002, undated (Box 12, Folder 36, Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Clergy: Nuns, circa 1970s, 1981-1992, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Comerford, Judge James, circa 1975, undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Connaughton, Terry, circa 1970s-1980s, undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Cooke, Terence Cardinal, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Cooney, Jerry, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Costello, Frank, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Crockett, Freddie, undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Crowley, Bob, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Cudahey, Dorothy Hayden, 1977, 1988-1989, 1997, undated (Box 12, Folder 44, Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Cudahey, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Culleton, Patrick, undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Cunningham, Willie Joe, 1975, 1986, 1991, undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Cushing, Cardinal Richard, 1977, circa 1982, undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - "D", circa 1960s-1980s, circa 1991-1992, 2000, undated (Box 12, Folder 49, Box 18, Folder 25-27, Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Daily, Bishop Thomas V., undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Daly, Bishop Cahal, 1991-1992, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Doherty, Joe, 1984-1991, 2003, undated (Box 12, Folder 52, Box 26, Folder 33, Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Doolan, Connie, 1986, c. 1990s, undated (Box 12, Folder 53, Box 23, Folder 37, Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Dow, William P., undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Duggan, Steve, undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Dunne, Ben, 1993, 1997, undated (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Durkan, Frank, 2000, undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - "E", 1982, 1987, 1998, circa 2000, undated (Box 12, Folder 58, Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Eames, Doctor Robin, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - "F", circa 1970s, 1981, 1988-1999, undated (Box 12, Folder 60, Box 18, Folder 28-30, Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Fanning, Charles, undated (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Fanning, Samuel, undated (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Finnegan, Paul, undated (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Fitzpatrick, Jim, undated (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Flannery, Michael, 1977, 1986, 1988, 1991, 1994, undated (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Flannery, Pearl, undated (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Flatley, Thomas J., undated (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Flynn, William J., 1994, undated (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - "G", circa 1970s, 1981-1990, 1994-1999, undated (Box 12, Folder 69, Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Galvin, Martin, undated (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Garvey, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Geary, William, undated (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Gleason, Thomas W. (Sr.), undated (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Glucksman, Loretta Brennan, 1993, 2000, undated (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Grace, J. Peter, circa 1970s, undated (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Guerin, Veronica, 1995-1996, 2003, undated (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Guinness, Desmond, 1992, undated (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - "H", circa 1970s, 1982-1990, 1995, 2000-2001, undated (Box 18, Folder 31-32, Box 12, Folder 78, Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Harrison, George, 1996, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Haughy, Charles, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - "I", 1982, 1989, 1999, 2001, undated (Box 12, Folder 80, Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Individuals General, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Irwin, Jack, 1986-1988, 1995, 1999, undated (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - "J", 1981, 1988, 1995, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 12, Folder 82, Box 27, Folder 4)
  - "K", circa 1975, 1980, 1988-1996, undated (Box 12, Folder 83, Box 18, Folder 33-36, Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Keating, Sean, undated (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Kelly, Dan, undated (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Kelly, Kevin (World of Hibernia Magazine), undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Kennedy, Joe, undated (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Kennedy, Kevin, undated (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Kennedy Jr., Robert F., undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - "L", circa 1975, 1987-1997, 2000, 2002, undated (Box 12, Folder 88, Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Lane, John, 1986-1987, undated (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Lawe, John - Cardinal O'Connor Dedicating Lauve Monument, undated (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Lewis, Lennox, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - "M", circa 1970s, circa 1982-1989, 1992-2001 (Box 18, Folder 37-41, Box 12, Folder 90, Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Mac Con Iomaire, Liam, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Mackin, Sean, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Macphaidan, Reverend Bartley, 1987, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Maloney, Reverend Patrick, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Mann, Michael (Yiddish Sons of Ireland), circa 1965, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Mannion, Patricia, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - McCourt, Frank, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - McDonagh, Kathleen, 1988, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - McDonald, Steven, 1987-1988, 1995, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - McElroy, Anna, 1980, 1989, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - McGonagle, Declan, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - McGuinness, Paschal, 1982, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - McGuire, Peter J., undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - McGuirk, Margie, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - McKiernan, Peter, 1986, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - McManus, Father Sean, circa 1970, 1980, 1982, 1987-1999, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - McMullen, Mary, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - McQuaid, Archbishop John Charles, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Meehan, Reverend Peter, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Melia, Aloysius, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Mockler, Frank T., undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Moore, Mary Holt, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Morrissey, Kevin, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Murphy, Annie, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - "N", 1984-1998, 2001-2003, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Newman, Paul, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)